And now, you were with your co-star in the new movie, Ryan Guzman?
Ryan Guzman, yeah.
All right. He’s a good-looking guy.
He’s very cute.
Have you seen this guy?
He’s so fun. He’s a real sweet, he’s a gentleman.
We’re doing all this promo together for the movie.
Mm hmm.
So we walked the carpet at the Globes together.
So there’s nothing going on?
No, no, no, no, no.
Cause people of course assume that cause you’re with him….
- Yeah.
- No, always, always.
No, but we arrived separately.
But then later we went to the parties together, and we had some fun.
And it was good.
Right.
Yeah.
Does he have a girlfriend?
I think he might. I’m not sure. I know he did.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
What?
I… No, I’m not, I’m just, I’m not in his business like that.
Uh-huh. Not yet.
You never know.
Now why not?
What’s the heck? What’s going on around here?
I don’t know. We just have all these posters laying around backstage.
Yeah. Just pop ‘em up.
Yeah. Um…
How old is he?
That’s very funny.
He’s … somewhere – I … 25, 26 maybe.
Seemed older.
Yeah. …. So much older.
Um. But see, that’s what the whole movie’s about, too.
There’s nothing wrong with that.
- And you talk about that in this issue of SELF Magazine.
- There’s nothing wrong with that.
- Is there nothing wrong with that? Yeah…
No, I hate that they have, like, a label for a woman who would date a younger guy.
If a younger guy’s interested in you, what’s the big deal?
But we… What’s the word for the man who’s, like, after the younger girls?
Right.
And, like, I’m not after younger guys.
If the younger guys like me, then that’s one thing, you know?
But there’s, like, guys who just go after younger women. They have no name, no label.
No, and they’ve been doing it forever.
And you can date one person.
Right.
Label.
Yeah.
Right?
And also maybe that’s just the person that you happen to get along with,
and even if it is more than one person, it doesn’t mean you should be labeled.
Right, right, I agree.
It just means that’s who you’re connecting with.
I think it’s a … there’s just a little bit of an imbalance. They’re not fair.